uncoverthenet.com 2013-06-18

# Privacy Policy - Uncover the Net

This privacy statement was first created on 11/27/2004 and updated on January 1, 2013. Uncover the Net has created this privacy statement in order to disclose our information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site, [www.uncoverthenet.com](http://www.uncoverthenet.com/). 

Upon reading this privacy statement, you will know:

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identifiable information is collected from you through the Web site.
  2. The organization collecting the information.
  3. How the information is used.
  4. With whom the information may be shared.
  5. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.
  6. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Uncover the Net's control.
  7. How you can access and correct any inaccuracies in the information collected about you.

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to the Uncover the Net site administrator by sending an email message to [support@uncoverthenet.com](mailto:support@uncoverthenet.com) or writing to us at the following address:

UTN Enterprises, Inc.  
340 S LEMON AVE #9861  
WALNUT, CA 91789 

To return to the Uncover the Net home page, please [click here](http://www.uncoverthenet.com/).

**Uncover the Net's Privacy Statement**  
Uncover the Net is the sole owner of the information it gathers on its site. UTN Directory will only share your information with outside parties in ways that are described in this privacy statement or if we are required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law, cooperate with law enforcement agencies, or comply with a legal process served on our Web site.

  * **Adding Your Site**  
We collect contact information such as name, email address, IP address, and company information such as company name, Web site description and URL. This information is used to add your website to the directory.
  *   

  * **Contacting Us**  
We use an email form located on the "contact us" page and other areas of the site to allow you to contact us directly with any questions or comments you may have. We read every message sent in and try to reply promptly to every one. This information is used to respond directly to your questions or comments. We may also file your comments to improve the site and functionality, or review and discard the information. Your personal information is only shared with third parties with your explicit permission.
  *   

  * **Newsletters**  
Individuals may subscribe to Uncover the Net's monthly email newsletter that provide updates about Uncover the Net and it's special offers, announcements and more. Your email address is used to send you these emails. To unsubscribe from the monthly newsletter, please [click here](http://www.uncoverthenet.com/newsletter/) and see the unsubscribe heading.
  *   

  * **Logged Files and Cookies**  
The Uncover the Net Web site logs IP addresses and browser types for search engine and reader trend purposes. These logs will be analyzed to improve the value of the directory. A user's session will be tracked, but the user will be anonymous. We do, however link IP addresses to any "site submissions" to track our sales and marketing campaigns. This information does not contain any personally identifiable information.

This Web site does use cookies in the forums.

**Third Party Links**  
Uncover the Net lists websites in virtually every subject available. Given the nature of the field that we are in, we link to thousands of different websites. Please note that these Web sites' privacy policies may differ from those of Uncover the Net. We encourage you to read the privacy statement of any Web site you may visit.

**How to Unsubscribe from Uncover the Net Email Publications**

  * **Newsletter**  
To unsubscribe from the monthly newsletter, please [click here](http://www.uncoverthenet.com/newsletter/) and see the unsubscribe heading.

**Security**  
Protecting your privacy and your information is a top priority at Uncover the Net. We have taken careful measures to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of your information and our database. Once we receive your information that was entered into our web site, it is stored into a secure mysql database. Your information is only accessible to our employees who need it in order to perform their jobs.

**Notification of Changes**  
If we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection through this Web site, we will notify you via email. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already collected through our site, we will post a prominent notice on our web site notifying users of the change.
